在近現代的日本
The near future Tokyo
這里有一群對抗惡魔的忍者
There was a group of ninjas who resisted an influx of demons
她們被稱作 對魔忍
They are called taimanin
本字幕由夜桜字幕組制作
時軸:颯
翻譯:樂月
其れは色の無い夜を染める
那就是被無色之夜所渲染
校對:雪夜
ただ無機質なる夜を染める
僅僅是被那無機質之夜所渲染
其れは下弦の月が照らした
在被這下弦之月所照耀之下的
壓制 雪夜
目に見える表の顔の色
眼睛能看得見表面的顏色
其れは色の無めい夜を染める
那就是被無色之夜所渲染
目に見えぬ裏の顔を染める
眼睛被無法望及的里側之色所渲染
最果ての空も埋めて二度と
就算將最盡頭的天空給埋藏著
消せない運命
也無法再次抹滅的命運
救いの無い此の身は
無法得到救贖的這副身體
誰かの意識の中で揺らめく
在誰的意識之中動搖著
紅に染まりさざめく世界
被渲染成紅色的喧鬧世界
重なり合う二つの記憶
重合起來的兩份記憶
決意を秘めた夜の影に
在隱藏著決意的夜之暗影中
剎那のゆらめき
感受到剎那間的動搖
對魔忍 Doujin
Taimanin Asagi doujin
黑暗的存在?妖魔正在侵蝕在魔都城?東京，與他們對抗的是正義的對魔忍阿莎姬
在市中心忽然出現的惡魔讓人們恐慌
One day, Demons suddenly appeared, in plain sight, at the center of the city. Waves of panic swept over the population.
現在城市中出現很多怪物
army of monster is rampaging throught the city.
形勢已經失去了控制
The situation is out of control.
啊～～啊～誰能救救我
Somebody, help me !.
哦 壞了
（Gasping sound）oh～no!
呀啊啊啊啊啊啊！
yaaaaaaaaa！！！！！
去死吧 惡魔！
DIE ! Demon！！！
你還好吧？
Are you all right?
站在我后面
Stand behind me.
我很快就能解決掉他們
I will take care of them.
Asagi你可別低估了你的敵人  哈啊！！！！！！！
Haaa !!! (Stabing)Don't turn your back to your enemy Asagi.
和我計劃的一樣 . 現在你的身體被封印了 .
As I planned, the poison sealed your ability.
即使你是最強的對魔忍.你也完全用不出力氣了.
Even if you are the strongest taimanin, you don't have the strength to resist now.
可惡！！Oboro！我不會原諒你的
dem！！！Oboro！I won't forgive you\b0}
啊！！！不！！放手啊  怪物！！
ahhhh！！！！！no！！！！！Let me go！
啊哈哈哈哈哈哈！！！這可是我的臺詞 Asagi！！
(laught) This should be my line !!! Asagi !!!
這一拳是為了死去的兄弟
This is for our brother you killed!
這一下為了我自己
And this one is for me!
讓她付出代價
Make her pay for her crime.
也～！！！為你的罪孽付出代價！
Yeah！！！！You're regret for all yours sins!
繼續攝像    我說話你聽不見么？
You! At the camera, want to live ?
我的天哪 嚇死人了！
My god, you scared me!
照我說的做
Do as I said\b0}
這次你可逃不掉了哦
You don't get to crawl away.
來吧妞 往哪兒跑
Come one now. Hold her still.
鐵鏈捆住她的手.你們就可以任意的蹂躪她了
I will tie her hand, this will make her more cooperative.
哎呦 你剛才的氣勢去哪了？
You're not so tought now. Hum ?
看她現在那個狼狽樣兒
she is in a real mess
玩夠了沒有 .臭婊子
Game over. Bitch
一滴不剩的給我喝下去NHurry up, swallow it down
給老子都吞下去啊
Gulp it all down.
下一位
Next
誰他媽的讓你休息了
Who said it was OK for you to rest.
用你的小嘴巴把所有大雞巴里的精液都唑出來  hahahah
Use your mouth to suck out everyone's cum. (Laught)
張嘴 把尿也喝下去 真聽話 小賤貨！
Drink it down！Yes, Yes Good Girl!
該去服務那邊了
05：21 : Serve the other side !
抬起頭看著我.還記得這個傷疤么？
Raise your head and look at me. Do you remember thoses scars?
你不是很牛屄么？
Not so thought now ? Bitch !
婊子 快唑雞巴
Suck on this.bitch
我快窒息了
I can't... breathe.
大雞巴太長了 已經插入我的胃里了
How long is he going to pump my throat ?
把我肏的大腦一片空白
My vision... is fading.
快他媽的要射了！
I am about to cum!
別干我了 饒了我吧！
No, let me go!
還不準把精液吞下去.用精液漱口
You're not allowed to swallow. Keep gargleing with my cum.
我吞下了一大口精液！
I am drowning in semen.
張嘴給老子看看. 很好  可以喝下去了
Open your mouth. Well, now you can drink it down
接著肏她！
Next
當然，我們還有很多舒服的事情要做，現在變得越來越有趣了。
Of course, we will have to work a lot more but that is fun actually.
你都拍攝下來了么？
(Laught) Did you record all of this ?
是的. 各種騷樣都錄進去了
yes.like this bitch face
接下來可是新東京 新聞時間了
Now, it's time for Tokyo news.
恭喜你即將成為今日頭條了
Congratulations. It seem you will be today hot topics.
我的天啊 這都是什么
My god, please, what's this
到底發生了什么事？？？
What's all this about?
哈哈哈 把真正的瘙樣展現給觀眾們看吧
(Laught). Don't be shy. Show your body to the audience.
Oboro 大人 叫你自我介紹.
Oboro SAMA told you to introduce yourself.
不要盯著我看啦
Please don't stare at me
你他媽的聽到沒有啊！
Did you hear that ！？
先向大家做個自我介紹吧
First, introduce yourself to the public.
你在大眾面前被干是不是很有感覺啊
Do this in public is really turn you on
我...我是....對魔忍...Asagi
I  .....I....Taimanin.....Asagi.....
你現在還不清楚自己的立場吧
You don't know your position right now
啊呀？你說什么呢 我們聽不清楚啊.
What? I can't hear you clearly.
大點聲告訴我們
Please speak a little louder.
我是對魔忍 叫做Asagi igawa
I'm a Taimanin, I'm called Asagi Igawa.
哈哈哈  沒想到曾經不可一世的對魔忍竟然落入如此境地
The once proud taimanin really fall out of grace.
我會連你現在僅存的驕傲都抹去
I'll wipe out what is left of your pride.
這些ORC濃厚的精液中含有讓女性催情的元素
Theses orcs dense cum is full of hormone that make women ovulate.
我被干的眼前一片漆黑.現在我只想要更多的大雞巴
My mind is completely blank.I just want more big dick
啊啊啊啊！！不要射在里面
Ahhhhh！！！Don't shoot it in
玩弄人類女性華潤細膩的身體真爽啊
This is a human female‘s  silky smooth skin
居然射進來這么多的精液 一定會懷孕的吧
So many came inside me, I am sure to get pregnant.
給老子生個ORC健康的獸人寶寶吧
You're going to give birth to an healthy orc baby.
這么多不同種類的怪物這她們得生出個什么怪胎
Everybody will get a chance to make her pregnant.
這些年來她可殺死了很多惡魔兄弟
Over the years she killed countless of our demons.
殺了她 肏死她
Kill her. Kill her. killing
今天她會為此用她的身體做出足夠的補償
And today she is going to offer reparation
（歡呼聲）
（cheer）
今后在她的余生她會一直為惡魔們生下各種各樣的崽子
She is going to give birth to demons child until the day she die
你在胡言亂語什么啊！？
10：19  What are you blabering about ?
現在我歡迎每一個來自東京的惡魔賦種于她
And I want every in Tokyo to also welcome demon seed in their bellies.
你沒有選擇.看看強大的對魔忍如何墮落在獸人的大雞巴之下
you don't have a choice, see how your mighty Taimanin fall before orc cocks
哈哈 簡直就像在使用飛機杯一樣暴力
Haha, she is like a masturbation toy.
該給寵物進食了
Time to feed the pet.
全都給我吃掉   哈哈哈啊哈哈
Come one, eat it for me, like a real DOG would.
給我用嘴叼回來 像真的寵物那樣 走你！
Here, go fetch this ball. go！
快走
go
只能用嘴哦
Just use your mouth
好了 .把她帶回到黃泉之原
All right, bring her back to Yomihara
遵命
Yes,Madam!
歡迎來到Oboro的地下監獄.這里將會直播Asagi的各種凌辱play
Welcome to Oboro lair. We will be streaming Asagi daily life as a cum dump.
你們想怎么蹂躪她可以來我的網頁來投票啊（www.patreon.com/opiumud 真能投啊 謝謝各位觀眾大佬參與投票和支持）
However, what's going to happen to her depends entirely of everyone vote.